

Tetiana Prylepska QA Engineer

Summary

I continuously improve my skills and develop my knowledge. While working as a frontend developer, I discovered my ability to pay attention to incomplete requirements and detect defects in source code, which sparked my interest in the area of product quality control. I am planning to develop my expertise in automated testing.

Contacts

- +380634761210
- tanyapavliuk1999@gmail.com
- Telegram
- LinkedIn
- Github
- Ukraine, Kyiv

Tech skills

- · HTML, CSS, SASS
- Tailwind CSS
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- React
- · Next.js
- Node.js
- **GIT**
- Jira
- Postman
- SQL

Soft skills

- · Team player
- Continuous learner
- Creative
- · Agile-oriented

Languages

- · English intermediate, study process
- Ukrainian native

Work experience

Frontend Developer

February 2024-April 2024

The "Kovcheg" shelter

Demo link

Technologies: React, Next.js, TailwindCSS, TypeScript, Sanity.

- · Designed and implemented reusable components and modules, optimizing website performance and scalability;
- Implemented functionalities and interfaces according to project and design requirements;
- · Actively participated in code reviews and discussions to enhance code quality and maintainability.

Intern Frontend Developer

November 2023-December 2023

SoftRyzen

Github link Demo link

Technologies: React, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Sanity.

- Implemented sanity.io for the ease of content management on the website;
- Developed reusable and extendable code, enhancing its maintainability and scalability;
- · Worked by Scrum methodology;
- Actively participated in code reviews and knowledge-sharing sessions.

Education

ITVDN

February 2024

TypeScript

· GoIT

Full Stack Developer

March 2023-December 2023

 Zhytomyr State Technological University October 2022 - December 2023 Master's degree, management

Project Experience

LearnLingo

Technologies: React, TailwindCSS, Formik, Firebase, Vite Key features of LearnLingo include user registration, teacher selection, and the ability to add preferred teachers to favorites for future sessions.

CarpTravel

Technologies: HTML, TailwindCSS, Next.js 13.

The website offers you unforgettable trips to the most beautiful parts of the Carpathians. The goal of this site provide information about the services of the company and draw new customers.

Movie

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JS, React, API.

The site provides information about the top 20 movies and details about actors and reviews. Also, it includes the functionality of searching movies by name.